(Elizabeth:)But then, I remembered
that I'd written it on my hand.
Lucky I didn't confuse it with
what I'd written on my other hand...
(Elizabeth:)...which are the coordinates
for a neutron star.
Because if I tried to go there,
I'd be crushed by hypergravity.
(Elizabeth:)-Anyway, hello.
-Hello.
(Elizabeth:)-Nice to finally meet you in person.
-I would imagine it is.
(Sheldon:)This is my friend and roommate,
Dr. Leonard Hofstadter.
(Leonard:)Hi-lo.
(Leonard:)Oops. I started to say hi, and then
I switched to hello in the middle.
It came out "hi-lo."
(Leonard:)Duh.
(Leonard:)It's nice to meet you.
(Leonard:)I've read both your books
and your papers.
(Leonard:)I'm Leonard.
I live here. You're brilliant.
(Sheldon:)I apologize.
He's only an experimental physicist.
(Elizabeth:)No need to apologize. Some of my
best friends are experimental physicists.
(Elizabeth:)Well, not my best friends.
But I know them.
(Elizabeth:)My best friend
is a molecular chemist named Wendy.